ep.se 2013-10-31

# Privacy statement - EPiServer Enterprise .NET CMS | E-Commerce...

EPiServer AB is committed to protecting your integrity. This privacy statement describes how data is collected and used on the website www.episerver.com.

This policy does not apply to other online or offline EPiServer AB sites, products or services. By visiting this website, you consent to the principles for collection and usage of information described in this privacy statement.

## Handling Personal Information

### General

The Personal Data Act (1998:204 Swedish law) came into force 1 October 1998 and was fully applied 1 October 2001. The act prevents the violation of personal integrity by processing personal data. Your permission is required for us to handle your personal information. EPiServer AB, company number 556208-3435, Regeringsgatan 67, 103 86 Stockholm, Sweden is responsible for the information provided to EPiServer AB and its subsidiaries.

### Use of Your Personal Information

By filling in web forms, providing registration details or, in any other way, providing EPiServer AB with personal information, you thereby approve the following conditions for the handling of your personal information. The personal information collected by EPiServer AB is used to be able to fulfill our commitment to you as a user of EPiServer AB's services, and to be able to maintain our customer registry. The information may also be used for customized information and for marketing purposes. Your personal information may be shared with EPiServer AB's partners, in certain cases outside the European Union, so that they will be able to send you information about their products and services. EPiServer AB can also distribute or deliver the personal information registry to a third party, if that third party either partly or fully takes over EPiServer AB's business activities.

EPiServer AB handles suitable personal information, e.g. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, to be able to provide any services without specific permission.

## Cookies on the Website

A cookie is a small text file that visited websites save on your computer. Cookies are used to provide visitors access to various functions. The information in the cookie can be used to track your internet usage. Under the Electronic Communications Act, all visitors to a website with cookies must have access to information stating that the website contains cookies and the purpose for which cookies are used.

### **Name of cookies, domains and purposes**

Name | Domain | Purpose  
---|---|---  
EPiServer.CMO.LPO | [www.episerver.com](http://www.episerver.com/) | Visitor behaviour and navigation for EPiServer CMO  
ASP.NET_SessionId | [www.episerver.com](http://www.episerver.com/) | This session cookie is essential for the website to operate and is set upon your arrival to the site. This cookie is deleted when you close the browser.  
BIGipServerwww.episerver.com  
_HTTP_Pool | [www.episerver.com](http://www.episerver.com/) | Used for load balancing purposes.  
.EPiTrace | [www.episerver.com](http://www.episerver.com/) | Visitor behaviour and navigation for EPiServer Live Monitor  
PREF | [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) | Google Analytics. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
_utma | [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) | Google Analytics. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
_utmb | [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) | Google Analytics. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
_utmc | [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) | Google Analytics. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
_utmz | [www.google.com](http://www.google.com/) | Google Analytics. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
_twitter_sess | [www.twitter.com](http://www.twitter.com/) | Share this on Twitter. Third-party cookie used to push links from the site to Twitter.  
munchkin.marketo.net/munchkin.js | [www.marketo.com](http://www.marketo.com/) | Marketo. Third-party cookie used to collect information about how visitors use the website.  
  
### **Cookies are used in the following situations on this Web site:**

  * If you choose to show the website in english and then for example choose change to swedish or other language, a cookie will be sent to remember your choice of language. 
  * If you answer/send in a form, a cookie will be sent to remember that you have sent a form. 
  * The website uses cookies in order to collect information about how the pages are used. 
  * Information about what server your PC is connected to, what type of browser, how often you have been visiting our website, what pages you have visited etc is stored. The information is used for the purpose of analyzing statistics regarding the use of the website.

### **To avoid cookies at the web site, you can as a visitor:**

  * Choose not to accept cookies in your browser settings, but then the web site will not be fully functional.
  * Avoid to answer forms. 
  * End your visit at the website.

## Analytics Tools for the Website

### Google Analytics

On this website the web analytics tool [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics "Google Analytics") is used to get an overall picture of how visitors use the site.

Google Analytics uses cookies to collect information in an anonymous form (aggregated) about how visitors use the website, for example, the number of page views, how visitors have arrived at the website, and the number of visits. The purpose is to help us improve the usability of the website. The information generated through your website usage is redirected to and stored by Google Inc. IP addresses are stored, but cannot be distinguished individually.

Google can transfer the collected information to a third party if it is required by law or in case a third party processes the information on Google’s account. Google cannot link IP addresses with other data held by Google.

### EPiServer CMO

To be able to optimize the content of the website we are using EPiServer CMO for campaign handling and optimization. EPiServer CMO collect information in an anonymous form (aggregated) about how visitors use the website, for example, the number of page views, how visitors have arrived at the website, and the number of visits.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also update the updated date at the bottom of the page. You will be informed of any important changes either via a message in a prominent place on the website's home page, or via notification sent directly to you. Please review the privacy statement at regular intervals to keep up-to-date with information on how we protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of this service means that you accept the privacy statement and any updates.

## Contact Information

If you require further information about EPiServer AB's privacy statement, contact our Personal Data Act via e-mail: 

* * *

Updated: 3/1/2013 8:42:24 PM
